<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie Catalog</string>

    <string name="movies">Movies</string>
    <string name="tvshow">TV Show</string>
    <string name="bahasa">Bahasa</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>

    <string-array name="data_title">
        <item>A Star Is Born</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>
        <item>Bird Box</item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>Bumblebee</item>
        <item>Creed</item>
        <item>Deadpool</item>
        <item>How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World</item>
        <item>Venom</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_desc">
        <item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers — and falls in love with — struggling artist Ally. She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer — until Jack coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Allys career takes off, the personal side of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his own internal demons.</item>
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people</item>
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. </item>
        <item>Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide, a survivor and her two children make a desperate bid to reach safety.</item>
        <item>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock n roll band Queen in 1970. </item>
        <item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred</item>
        <item>The former World Heavyweight Champion Rocky Balboa serves as a trainer and mentor to Adonis Johnson, the son of his late friend and former rival Apollo Creed.</item>
        <item>Deadpool tells the origin story of former Special Forces operative turned mercenary Wade Wilson, who after being subjected to a rogue experiment that leaves him with accelerated healing powers, adopts the alter</item>
        <item>As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless’ discovery of an untamed, elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at home and Hiccup’s reign as village chief is tested</item>
        <item>Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following a scandal, but accidentally becomes the host of Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon, he must rely on his newfound powers to protect</item>
    </string-array>


    <array name="data_poster">
        <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="data_tvshow_title">
        <item>The Arrow</item>
        <item>Fairytail</item>
        <item>The Flash</item>
        <item>Game of Thrones</item>
        <item>Gotham</item>
        <item>Hanna</item>
        <item>Ncis</item>
        <item>Riverdale</item>
        <item>Shameless</item>
        <item>Supergirl</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_tvshow_desc">
        <item>Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht is lost at sea. He returns five years later a changed man, determined to clean up the city as a hooded vigilante armed with a bow.</item>
        <item>Long ago in the mountains, a fighting master known as Gohan discovered a strange boy whom he named Goku. Gohan raised him and trained Goku in martial arts until he died. The young and very strong boy was on his</item>
        <item>After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is struck by lightning and falls into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of super speed, granting him the ability to move</item>
        <item>Seven noble families fight for control of the mythical land of Westeros. Friction between the houses leads to full-scale war. All while a very ancient evil awakens in the farthest north. Amidst the war, a neglected</item>
        <item>Before there was Batman, there was GOTHAM. Everyone knows the name Commissioner Gordon. He is one of the crime worlds greatest foes, a man whose reputation is synonymous with law and order. But what is known</item>
        <item>This thriller and coming-of-age drama follows the journey of an extraordinary young girl as she evades the relentless pursuit of an off-book CIA agent and tries to unearth the truth behind who she is. Based on the</item>
        <item>From murder and espionage to terrorism and stolen submarines, a team of special agents investigates any crime that has a shred of evidence connected to Navy and Marine Corps personnel, regardless of rank or position.</item>
        <item>Set in the present, the series offers a bold, subversive take on Archie, Betty, Veronica and their friends, exploring the surreality of small-town life, the darkness and weirdness bubbling beneath Riverdales wholesome</item>
        <item>Chicagoan Frank Gallagher is the proud single dad of six smart, industrious, independent kids, who without him would be... perhaps better off. When Franks not at the bar spending what little money they have, he…</item>
        <item>Twenty-four-year-old Kara Zor-El, who was taken in by the Danvers family when she was 13 after being sent away from Krypton, must learn to embrace her powers after previously hiding them. The Danvers teach her to</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="data_tvshow_poster">
        <item>@drawable/poster_arrow</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon_ball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_flash</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_god</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_gotham</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hanna</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_ncis</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_riverdale</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_shameless</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_supergirl</item>
    </array>
</resources>
